

#### **Portfolio**

Link to my portfolio here

### Front-end Back-end

Html Node.js

CSS **Express** 

**Tailwind CSS NestJS** 

Chakra UI MySQL

**Javascript TypeORM** 

**TypeScript** NoSQL

Docker Angular

React

**NextJs** 

**React Native** 

#### Other Skills

GitHub

GitLab

**Figma** 

Agile method

Team player

## Languages

French: Mother tongue

English: B2 Upper intermediate

#### Contact



Brussels



0472 09 40 56



leopoldvde@hotmail.com

# Léopold van der Elst



# Full-Stack Developer | Web & Mobile

#### **Profile**

Hi, I am Léopold, a 23 year old full stack developer with a passion for learning and improving my skills. I have acquired my skills by attending two bootcamps and more recently by working in a company. I have learned to adapt and grow independently. The idea of discovering new challenges and new projects always motivates me.

# **Experiences**

#### Intuitim | 04/2023 - 10/2023

Full-Stack Web Developer

Medical imaging product core functionality development

- Feature development and debugging
- Code review
- Unit testing
- · User story and task definition
- · Daily stand-up
- · Sprint planning

Angular, TypeScript, NestJS, MySQL, Docker, Gitlab

#### Green SA | 08/2022 - 10/2022

Administrative assistant for a photovoltaic panel installer company

- · Customer contact
- · Site organisation
- Installation monitoring

#### Education

#### La Capsule | 10/2022 - 12/2022

2 month bootcamp

Certification: Web & Mobile Application Development Project

Manager - Level 6

Html, Css, Javascript, React, React Native, Express, Nodejs, MongoDb

Wild Code School | 03/2021 - 07/2021

5 month bootcamp

Html, Css, Javascript, React, React Native, Express, Nodejs, MySQL

Jury Central Savutus | 2018/2021

Certification: CESS computer science option